[thunder rumbling]
[Elmo] "Storm on Sesame Street."
- Let's get another.
- Okay. Almost, Bert.
[both straining]
- Oh, boy, this is heavy.
- [Ernie] Okay. Phew.
[sighs]
- Come on in, get your supplies.
- Thanks for the water.
- Certainly, Baby Bear.
- You're welcome. Stay safe, Baby Bear.
- [barking]
- Oh, hi.
Elmo's so happy you're here.
You know, there's a big storm
coming to Sesame Street,
so we're helping our neighbors.
Like Elmo said,
we're handing out extra food and water,
'cause folks will need
to stay inside during the storm.
- Yeah.
- Be safe, everyone.
- Uh-huh.
- Together, we'll all get through this.
You know, Daddy says
there's gonna be lots of wind
and rain, and thunder and lightning.
[gasping]
Elmo and Tango
don't want this storm to come, Daddy.
Yeah, I understand.
But unfortunately,
we can't change the weather.
We can prepare for it, though,
which is why I need your help,
uh, on a special mission.
- Wha… A special mission?
- [Louie] Mm-hm.
- [exciting music playing]
- I need you to find star stickers,
a sock and an ice cream scooper.
- [Tango] Mm?
- Huh?
[laughing] I know, they… they seem silly.
But I promise they'll help us
and our friends during the storm.
Helping our friends is how
we can show courage during tough times.
Well, you can count on us.
Elmo and Tango
can show courage, just like Daddy.
I know it. I know you can.
Okay, now come on.
Let's start our special mission.
- [giggling]
- [barking]
[news theme music playing]
I'm Sammy Squalls, here on Sesame Street,
where neighbors are helping each other
prepare for the really big storm.
Excuse me, what are your thoughts
on the oncoming storm?
Scram.
Yes, absolutely.
We'd all love for this storm to scram.
Not the storm, you.
Oh! Any thoughts on the oncoming storm?
Double scram. [laughing]
[in squeaky voice] Okay. There you…
[in normal voice] There you have it.
Back to you.
Okay, I found some more supplies. Here.
[Cookie Monster] Oh, good.
[Snuffy] That one's cute, Bird.
They're so cute.
Ah, Snuffy, Big Bird. Hi.
- [chuckling] Hi, Elmo.
- Hey, Elmo.
It's really busy in here.
Looks like lots of people
are staying at Elmo's for the storm.
- Yeah.
- [Abby] Hey, Elmo.
Oh! Coming!
[barking]
Hey, Abby, Rudy, have you seen a…
[shivering]
Abby, oh, I'm so scared.
Everything feels so different outside.
I know, brother. I know.
Rudy's right. Sesame Street
does feel different today.
Hm. Elmo understands why Rudy's scared.
Can Elmo tell you something?
Elmo's scared too.
But Elmo needs to have courage.
Yeah, Elmo has to help his friend.
Elmo has an idea.
Uh, Rudy, Abby, do you want
to help Elmo and Tango
with our special mission?
- [exciting music playing]
- [both] Huh? Special mission?
Yeah, Elmo's daddy needs us
to find three things: star stickers…
- Uh-huh.
- Oh.
…a sock and an ice cream scooper.
Elmo doesn't know why, but his daddy
said that they're very important.
Whoa! This must be
a really special mission, then.
[thunder crashing]
It's okay.
Aw! But the storm…
- Is outside.
- Mm-hm.
And we're inside.
- So let's start our special mission.
- [exciting music playing]
To the kitchen!
Okay.
There you go, Radar.
- Hi.
- Oh!
Hi, Snuffy!
[Snuffy] Whoa!
What are you three doing there?
- Well, we're on a special mission.
- Oh?
- Wow. Why so many stuffies?
- Yeah, what's with the stuffies, Snuffy?
Well, storms can be scary, you know.
And you never know
when you might need a hug.
And I like to get mine
from a fuzzy cabbage.
[Abby] Aw.
Um, you said something
about a special mission?
Yeah, that's right.
We're looking for star stickers.
- They're very important.
- [exciting music playing]
But we don't know why.
Will you help us look?
- Oh, sure.
- You betcha.
Great. Thank you.
- [Abby] I'm gonna look over here.
- Excuse me.
- [wind gusting]
- Whoa!
Oh, that wind is so loud and scary.
It is scary. Elmo's scared too.
But Elmo needs to have courage
and help his friends.
Maybe with a fuzzy hug.
See? That wasn't the wind, Rudy.
That was just dragon roaring for a hug.
Oh! A dragon! I like that.
Oh! Look! There's the stickers!
Yeah!
[all exclaiming happily]
All right, come on. There's more
to find on our special mission.
Yeah, that's right. We have to find
a sock and an ice cream scooper.
And Elmo knows where to look next:
Bert and Ernie's apartment. Yay!
Oh! Ernie, Bert, we need help with our…
special…
mission.
Yeah, that's right.
Bert, it's a really important mission,
okay?
[Bert] Rudy, we're over here.
- The animals stole our laundry.
- Give me that.
- Why do you have all these animals?
- Stop, you!
Well, we're taking care of them
during the storm. See?
We're giving them food and water
and a safe place to stay.
And they're giving us nothing but trouble.
Come back here!
Hey, look, look, look! A sock!
Oh! Could we have that sock, Ernie?
[grunting] Oh, sure you can.
What? Oh! If you can catch it.
[groaning]
- [thunder rumbling]
- [all gasping]
That thunder is so loud and scary.
- [gentle music playing]
- The storm is getting scary.
But Elmo needs to have courage
for his friends.
Hey, Rudy, look.
The sound of the thunder is scary.
- Yeah.
- But this isn't.
[rattling]
[giggling]
Grab an instrument, everybody.
- Huh? Whoa.
- [gentle tune playing]
[Abby] Aw.
Well, look at that.
Your idea helped the animals feel better.
- You helped me feel better too, Elmo.
- [exciting music playing]
- Thank you.
- Aw, you're welcome.
[Abby giggling]
And…
we got the sock!
[all] Yay!
Now, let's go back upstairs
to Elmo's apartment.
Yeah, we still need to get
the ice cream scooper.
- Oh, yeah, that's right.
- Bye.
Bye now!
So, uh, you wanna play checkers, Bert?
[Bert] Ernie, I'm over here.
[snickering]
Phew! It is really raining out there.
Thanks so much for inviting me in.
Oh, happy to have you.
Oh, Sammy Squalls! In my apartment! Oh!
Tonight's top story: your place is lovely!
- Aw.
- Oh! Thank you so much. Oh!
And this just in: Yuck. [groaning]
Pleasure as always, Oscar.
Is there a good place for my go bag?
- You put it down right there.
- Okay.
Good idea having a bag packed to take
with you in case the storm gets worse
and you need to go quickly.
Oh, yes. Our go bag
has all our most important stuff.
Phones, medicine, food, water.
Oh, yeah.
That's kind of like my scram bag.
It has all my most important stuff:
- smelly trash.
- [Mae] Ugh!
Oh, wow. Okay.
Ms. Sammy Squalls, let's find you
a less stinky place to rest, huh?
- [Cookie Monster] Way ahead of you.
- Oh!
- What are you doing?
- Oh, we inflating this bed.
Yeah, just unfurl it here.
And me going to turn it on.
Oh, good. This is working.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, it's working a little too well.
Okay, you can turn it off now.
- It's a little big.
- Breaking news: I'm getting squished.
Oh, yeah. Nice and comfy. Yeah.
Help me.
Elmo, how'd your special mission go?
Well, we got the star stickers
and the sock.
- Yeah.
- But no ice cream scooper yet.
- Then you better keep lookin'.
- Yeah.
You know, speaking of looking,
has anybody seen my microphone?
It got lost when I got squished.
It might have fallen in my scram bag here.
- Let me check.
- Yeah!
Let's see.
We got an old hairbrush, an old tuba,
a dirty boot, an ice cream scooper.
Oh, an even dirtier boot.
Wait a minute, Oscar. We need that.
What, the dirtier boot?
I knew you couldn't be all bad, Elmo.
Sure. Here.
No, no, no, the ice cream scoop.
Hey! We found all three items.
- Yes! We did it!
- Oh! All right!
[thunder rumbling]
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, no.
Oh, looks like the power's out.
Yeah.
Everyone all right?
Elmo?
Where are you, son?
[gentle music playing]
Elmo's scared of the big storm, Daddy.
Elmo tried to have courage,
but the storm is too scary.
[thunder rumbling]
Oh, here. Come on.
Take my hand, son.
There we go. Now, squeeze it three times.
- Count with me?
- Okay.
[both] One. Two. Three.
[both sigh]
You know,
the storm scares me too.
Really? Daddy gets scared?
But Daddy has so much courage.
I do. And so do you.
Courage is feeling scared
and still helping others.
And you've done that.
You did a great job helping Rudy.
You got a lot of courage, son.
I'm proud of you.
Oh. Thank you, Daddy.
[both laughing]
Oh, here, give me those stickers
you found on your special mission.
- Okay. Here you go.
- All right.
Everybody, uh, put these stickers
on your flashlights
just like this.
Now, check this out.
[Elmo] Oh…
- [Louie laughing]
- [all exclaiming]
[Louie] Huh?
It's good to be together.
Together, we can get through anything.
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, the storm may be outside ♪
♪ But we're right here and by your side ♪
♪ If you're scared or have a fright ♪
♪ We'll hold you close and tight ♪
♪ Let the thunder crack and boom ♪
[thunder rumbling]
♪ We're together inside this room ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ When we're together
We'll get through any weather ♪
♪ I'm here, I'm here for you ♪
♪ Let's laugh and have some fun ♪
[Grover giggling]
♪ Wait until the storm is done ♪
♪ Our friends are all around ♪
♪ This is where the love is found ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh ♪
♪ Whoa, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Elmo believes, believes in you ♪
♪ With courage we'll make it through ♪
♪ When we're together
We'll get through any weather ♪
♪ Together me and you ♪
[Tango howling]
[giggles]
Wait a minute.
Daddy, what did we need
the ice cream scoop for?
Oh… [laughs] Of course!
Well, for the most important thing of all.
Ice cream, everyone!
- [Ernie] Oh yeah!
- [Big Bird] Wow! Ice cream!
- Oh, Elmo loves ice cream.
- Yeah.
And Elmo really loves his friends.
We can weather anything together.
[Mae] All right, Alan, get scoopin'.
- [thunder cracks]
- [wind whistling]
[Abby] Oh, no, Elmo, look at our street.
The sign!
Oh. There you are.
It's good to see you on Sesame Street,
but Sesame Street
doesn't really look like Sesame Street.
Yeah. Everything's different
after the big storm.
[news theme music playing]
Reporter Sammy Squalls here,
live on Sesame Street.
And after the storm,
there is a lot to fix here.
Fallen trees, flooded apartments.
It just doesn't look like the neighborhood
we all know and love.
And this reporter has to wonder,
when will Sesame Street
feel like home again?
- [groans] You're back?
- Yuck.
Okay, um, Oscar, what do you think?
When will Sesame Street feel
like home again? And don't say scram.
[groans] Well, if I can't say scram,
he will.
Scram!
[both laughing]
Um… [clears throat] Let's ask someone
who's a little less grouchy.
Oh. It doesn't feel like home.
And I really want to help.
But the problem is so big. What can we do?
- [heroic music plays]
- Oh!
What if Elmo and Abby were superheroes?
- Huh?
- Then we could totally help Sesame Street!
Yeah! Let's do it!
But wait. We still need one thing.
Aha!
Elmo, are those your pillow cases?
Not anymore. They're our superhero capes.
- Huh?
- Elmo will be…
- [heroic music playing]
- Super Elmo with super strength!
And I am Super Abby with super speed!
And she's Super Tango
with super cute ears.
[panting]
Dun-da-da-daa!
C'mon, Super Abby and Super Tango!
Let's make Sesame Street
feel like home again!
Yes!
- Cookie Monster.
- Oh, yeah, hi.
- Hi. Can you help me answer a question?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
Awesome. When do you think
that Sesame Street
will start to feel like home again?
Oh, okay. Well, me think that--
- Da-da-da…
- Uh…
- Yes? Oh, okay.
- Excuse me second.
Grover, what you doing?
I am building a rocket ship
to go to the moon.
They do not have any storms there.
So, moon, here I come. [laughs]
Grover, are you sure you can go
to the moon in this thing?
Of course I am sure.
Well, my rocket ship is ready.
That is supposed to do that.
Before you go, Grover,
can I interview you about the storm?
Nope. Because there will be
no storms where I am going.
See you soon, moon.
In three, two, one, blast off!
[rattling]
Whoa.
[clattering]
Am I on the moon?
- Uh, no.
- Ugh.
Dun-da-da-da!
Super Abby and Super Tango,
we need to find a way
to help Sesame Street.
Yes, we're going to make it feel
like home again!
[groans]
How's a Grouch supposed to be grouchy
when he has to deal with all this?
Oh, just like that. Heh, heh, heh.
Look! Our sign fell down.
Maybe we can use
our superpowers to fix it.
Oh! Yeah!
Elmo can use his super strength!
[heroic music playing]
[straining]
Try this way.
[clattering]
[groaning]
That wasn't very super.
[sighs] Elmo doesn't know
if he can help with a job this big.
[Slimey moaning sadly]
What's going on, Slimey?
Aw, it's his clothes.
When the storm hit,
they got all scattered in the wind.
[Abby] Aw.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, hey!
Hey, Elmo found your sweater.
Look at this! I found your little hat.
And Tango found your shirt.
Itty-bitty pajamas!
A tiny sneaker.
And eensy-weensy polka-dotty pants!
Go!
Thank you!
You're welcome, Slimey.
[sighs] But Elmo just helped a little.
Oh. Super Elmo and Super Abby still need
to find a big way to help Sesame Street.
Yeah. And make it feel like home again.
Dun-da-da-da!
And so, we're working as fast as we can
to get the lights on in your apartment.
Aw, thanks, Calvin.
Yeah. We really appreciate
all you utility workers are doing
to keep us safe after the storm.
- Yeah.
- Well, that's our job.
Yeah. Mm.
Bert? Ernie?
What happened?
Oh, all that rain from the storm
flooded our apartment.
Almost everything we own is ruined.
Yeah, including all my joke books.
I mean, look at this.
Hey, Bert. Knock, knock.
- Who's there?
- I don't know!
Aw.
Ernie and Bert, Elmo's so sorry.
But the good news is we can help.
- Because we're superheroes.
- [heroic music playing]
Yeah. And I can use my super speed.
I will run, run, run
around your apartment,
waving my arms really fast in the air
until it blows your stuff nice and dry!
Woo-hoo! Swish, swish,
swish, swish, swish, swish!
Dry, dry, dry, dry.
Woo-hoo. Wha-hoo-hoo-ha!
So how's it look? Are they dry?
Um…
- No. Still pretty wet.
- I'll try one more time.
Swish, swish, swish, whoo! [laughing]
[clattering]
[groans]
That wasn't so super.
Aw, thanks for trying, Abby.
But it'll be okay.
We have help drying out our place.
Yeah, but even once it's dry, we still
lost a lot of stuff we'll never get back.
I'm just…
I'm just so sad.
Oh, I'm sorry, Ernie.
I'd be sad too
if my favorite things got ruined.
I just wish I had my jokes back.
They always make me feel better.
[gasps] Well, I could tell you
my favorite joke.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Yeah. Okay…
Um, if you have 10 apples in one hand
and 12 oranges in the other,
what have you got?
Uh, what?
Big hands.
[all laughing]
- Bert! I love it! Oh, Abby!
- Yes!
I'm gonna remember that
and write it down in my new joke book.
Oh, thank you, Abby.
Aw, you're welcome, Ernie.
But I just helped a little.
Yeah, we still have to keep looking
for the one big thing we can do
to help Sesame Street
feel like home again.
Maybe there's a way for Super Elmo
and Super Abby to help at Hooper's.
Come on.
Dun-da-da…
[all] Aw. Oh, no!
Super Abby?
Elmo's not sure
we can fix a problem this big.
We're not real superheroes.
We don't have superpowers,
so we can't help.
[sighs]
We tried all day
to make Sesame Street feel like home.
Maybe it never will.
- [objects clattering]
- Huh? What?
- Grover, you are making me very nervous.
- Be careful.
Grover? What is Grover doing?
Going to the moon, Elmo.
And yes, before you ask,
of course I will send you a postcard.
[Elmo giggling]
Uh, Grover, how are you going
to go to the moon?
Your boosters are boots.
I am certainly not staying here.
On the moon, there are no storms.
You want to go where there are no storms?
Yes, exactly.
On Sesame Street,
another storm could come.
And the last time, I was so scared.
I do not want to feel that way again.
Yeah, Grover's right.
The storm was really scary.
Elmo was scared too.
But we're here for you, Grover.
- Yeah, all your friends are.
- Yeah.
Really?
Yes. Really.
Um, can Elmo give Grover a hug?
I would like that.
[clattering]
- Whoa!
- Oh, dear.
Yeah. Probably for the best
I did not fly anywhere in that.
But thank you. That hug helped.
Aw.
We just helped a little.
No matter what Elmo and Abby tried,
we couldn't find one big way
to help Sesame Street.
But I did not need something big.
Just one little hug helped me feel better.
Yeah, and that joke you told me
might have seemed like one little thing.
But it really, really helped us.
Mm-hm.
Finding Slimey's clothes
helped him feel better too.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It might seem little, but…
Tha-a-a-a…
Ugh.
Thank you.
Uh, yeah, what he said.
When a neighborhood like ours
goes through something really hard…
it's not gonna get fixed by a superhero
swooping in and saving the day.
It'll be us helping each other.
That's right, Chris. And you know what?
You do not have
to have superpowers to help.
Now see? You already did
help your friends just by being you.
- Yeah.
- But what we did was so little.
It really made a big difference?
[chuckles] Come on,
let me show you something. Come on.
- Okay.
- 'Kay.
I want you to look around. Hm?
- Good.
- And see that one little help
becomes another little help,
which inspires everyone else
to help in the ways they can too.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Big Bird, can I help you?
- Yes, Mrs. Elmo's mom.
- All right.
- Bye, Big Bird.
- Bye-bye.
- Oh, hi, Mr. Post Malone.
- Hey there, Elmo. Abby, how we doing?
- Hi.
Oh, thank you so much
for coming to Sesame Street
to help us clean up our home.
Absolutely. I'm more than happy to do it.
You know,
Elmo thinks that maybe
a little help is all it takes
to make our street a better place.
♪ A little help, a little help ♪
♪ A little help is all it takes
To make our street a better place ♪
♪ A little help, a little help ♪
♪ A little help is all it takes
To make our street a better place ♪
♪ We can go through something hard ♪
♪ But I know we'll make it through ♪
♪ 'Cause you will always be there for me
And I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Oh, your kindness and compassion ♪
♪ I see them shining through ♪
♪ A little help, a little help ♪
♪ A little help is all it takes
To make our street a better place ♪
[all chattering]
- Oh, Elmo.
- Huh?
I've been looking for someone
to finally answer my question.
So when do you think Sesame Street
will start to feel like home again?
Hmm.
Well, Elmo thinks
that maybe home isn't a place.
Maybe home is the people,
and as long as we're all together,
Sesame Street will always feel like home.
[Alan] That's right. So let's eat.
Who wants a roll?
Oh, Elmo's pretty hungry.
[upbeat music playing]
[music fades out]